4psitelink.com 2011-10-06

# yLink by 4Psite :: Privacy

| 

## Privacy Notice

The web site you have entered, www.4PsiteLink.com, is operated by or on behalf of 4Psite, LLC is committed to protecting your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of information that is collected by 4PsiteLink on this web site, and how we use and protect it. This Policy also tells you what to do if you do not want your Personal Information collected when you visit our web site, and how you can change information you have already provided to us. This Policy applies only to the 4PsiteLink web sites listed here. For example, it does not apply to banners, sweepstakes and other advertisements or promotions we may sponsor or participate in on web sites owned by third parties. 

## Your Consent to This Privacy Policy

By using our web site, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted in this area of the site. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not provide any Personal Information (defined below) on this site. If you choose not to provide Personal Information on this site, you may not be able to do certain things, like access particular areas of the site, obtain certain services or send us e-mail. 

## Collection of Personal Information

As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means personally identifiable information such as the name, street address, telephone number, credit card information, screen name and email address of yourself or your customers. The site you entered may collect some of all of these types of Personal Information. Please be assured that 4PsiteLink will not collect any Personal Information from your visits to our sites unless you provide this information voluntarily. When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of the Personal Information as described in this Policy (see "Who to Contact" below). The site you entered may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (e.g., the site might allow you to send an electronic "post card" to a friend, in which case we will need that person's name and e-mail address). Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g., to mail the post card) and we will not contact the third party again by e-mail unless and until the third party contacts us. 

## How We Use Your Information

When you supply Personal Information at this web site, the brand whose site you entered will use it for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to provide you with a specific service or to send you a message). It may also be used by the brand whose site you entered, as well as by our other brands, to contact you regarding other products and services that may be of interest to you (including those we may offer jointly with other companies). (For more information on 4PsiteLink and its brands, see the paragraph about 4PsiteLink at the end of this Policy.) At any time, however, you may opt out of such future contact. (See "Who to Contact" below.) At times we may retain third parties to analyze data we collect on our web sites, including Personal Information, solely to help us improve our products and our web sites. In addition, if you order a product or service from us, we may share Personal Information with suppliers and other third parties to allow delivery of such product or service. These suppliers and other third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way. Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order. 

## Other Information We May Collect

You may have heard of "cookies," which are files or pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. 4PsiteLink may use cookies to ensure proper user identification, collect other information during your visit to our web site, such as the particular site areas you visit and the products or services you buy through our web site. We collect this information for confidentiality purposes and to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs. Cookies may also be used to help speed up your future activities at our site; the computer can remember that you have already provided Personal Information to us and will not request that you provide any a second time. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Refusal of cookies at the site you entered may result in an inability to visit certain areas of the site or to receive personalized information when you visit the site. In addition, we are constantly trying to improve how we promote our web sites. To help us do this, we may measure the effectiveness of our web presence by determining what you clicked on to get to our site. Information about your computer, such as your IP address (a number assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Internet), the type of Internet browser you are using and the type of computer operating system you are using may also be collected and linked to your Personal Information. This is to ensure that our web sites present the best web experience for visitors, and that they are an effective information resource. Finally, we may supplement the information that you provided us with other information that we receive from third parties. We do this for marketing purposes in order to provide more targeted products and service to meet your needs. 

## Security of Information 

We take reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure. All personally identifiable information is subject to restricted access to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse. 

## Changes in Our Policy 

4PsiteLink reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. We will post any new policy here and we encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. 

## Who to Contact 

Please write to us at info@4psitelink.com or call us at (858) 433-0403 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or to report any violations of the Privacy Policy. We will respond to you within 24 to 48 hours in most cases.
